# Muhammad Ibnuh

Indonesia



ibnuhdev@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/ibnuh

# Summary

M. Ibnu Luthfi Azhar - Specializes in backend-development, I appreciate clean and easy to maintain code. Having strong skills to develop perfect solutions for complex logic using the newest technologies.

I've been working on many startups, building applications with other teams across countries remotely. I'm a fast learner, strikes to follow best practices and wrote well-documented software.

# **Experience**



# Software Engineer

The Software Practice Pte Ltd

Dec 2018 - Present (3 years 2 months +)

- Leads a team of developers to develop application seamlessly
- Contributes in the development of products through the software lifecycle, from early requirements to successful deployment
- Collaborates with developers from other countries on remote terms
- Responsible for application deployment and reliability

Main role & tech stack: C#, .NET Core, Svelte, VueJS, SQL Server, MySQL, Azure, AWS, Gitlab CI/CD, System Administrator, Lead Developer

#### Web Developer

Aug 2017 - Sep 2018 (1 year 2 months)

- Led the development team to develop the application from scratch
- Conduct various research for the application goals
- Integrated many services including Google Vision API, Stripe, PayPal, and more
- Manage the application deployment and setup the base for production environtment using Ubuntu Linux and Nginx web server

Tech stack: PHP, MySQL, Laravel, VueJS, Bash, Google Vision, Elasticsearch



#### Web Developer

#### Cangkirware

Jun 2017 - Apr 2018 (11 months)

- Responsible for the application development on various projects
- Direct contact with clients to discuss requirements and goals
- Led developers to develop many web applications from scratch

Tech stack: PHP, Wordpress, MySQL, Laravel, CodeIgniter

## Freelancer

Cangkirware

Feb 2016 - Jun 2017 (1 year 5 months)

- Responsible for the application development on various projects
- Direct contact with clients to discuss requirements and goals
- Finished 4 projects from scratch during the internship

Tech stack: PHP, Wordpress, MySQL, Laravel, Codelgniter

#### **Education**



### Universitas Muhammadiyah Riau

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology Nov 2020 - Mar 2024

# SMK Negeri 2 Pekanbaru

High School Diploma, Software Engineering 2014 - 2017

#### **Skills**

Program Development • Web Development • HTML • Microsoft Office • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • PHP • Management • Laravel • CodeIgniter

#### **Honors & Awards**



## Envato Helpful Hacker - Envato

Feb 2018

Got listed on Envato Product Security Honor Roll for finding and reporting critical vulnerability in the https://elements.envato.com system.

Name: Muhammad Ibnuh — @ibnuhx

Dates of reports: 27 Feb 2018

https://webuild.envato.com/helpful-hacker